I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Gosh, it's noisy...
Oh no, it's started!
Hey, you!
Yikes! I guess we can't
ride the gondola.
They've still got
the band member's story telling.
Hey, it's the kid.
Rikiya-kun!
Didn't think I'd ever see you
standing on that stage.
I didn't expect to see you, either.
I'll be there watching you.
Give it your best shot!
Thank you.
Oh, and give my regards
to Ryusuke-kun too.
How 'bout Chiba-kun?
Hmph!
-That wasn't good.
-Yeah...
Oh, there you are!
Hey! Koyuki!
Maho! When did you get here?
A little while ago.
The grounds are huge!
Yeah, it's quite big.
We'll be performing here...
This stage in the back.
There're three big stages.
Looks like there're
several smaller ones too.
Uh-huh.
Each band plays on each stage
at the same time.
Hmm. Won't the sound be mixed up?
Aw, I wanna see
Husking Bee from 3 PM.
The stages are far from each other
so it won't be mixed up.
There are trees too.
Wow, Oil Octopus is going to play...
-We're going to be on the 3rd stage, at 6:00.
-Wow, Apple will be playing too!
Yeah.
Hey, BECK and Yoshito
are playing at the same time!
Really?!
These two stages are far from each other,
so we can only see one stage.
I would take Yoshito on the main stage.
He's my classmate.
I'm dying to see Malcolm
on the second stage!
-Um, Ryusuke-kun...
-Ryusuke?!
Um, I'd rather not hear about him.
Huh? Is something wrong?
He's been really edgy
since last week...
I haven't seen him since
we argued over the phone.
-Maho, which...
-Koyuki! Good luck!
Actually, we'll be...
Hello?
Ah, Yoshito!
Really? You're staying
at the suite room?
Yeah, we're coming!
See ya, Koyuki-kun!
Yeah.
I wonder which stage
Maho-chan's coming to see.
Hmm.
Ooh, it's cold!
This could stop your heart! Serious!
They're counting the
number of people there.
There is no way we could get a bigger
audience than Eiji's band or Malcolm!
Yeah, the facilities are different too.
That deal you made
with Leon is outrageous!
If we lose this bet, the only
option left is for us to disband.
I wonder if there are any good ideas.
I still believe in the possibility.
What is it with this
"possibility" of yours?
You mean Koyuki's song?
It's the dream.
-Uh...Dream?
-Eek!
That dream we all saw.
That was definitely an omen.
A dream! You idiot!
I never saw such a dream!
Chiba!
-Chiba...
-Uh...
Maybe you weren't meant
to be a part of this band.
"Weren't meant to be
a part of this band?"
What the hell
are you talking about?
Every member is needed in BECK.
Ryusuke, what we saw was just a dream.
It's true this area is littered
'cause the people have no manners...
It's okay, Taira-kun...
The guy who created BECK says so...
So I'll...
-Hey, Chiba! Chiba, wait!
-Dammit!
It really bothered him that he was
the only one who didn't see that dream.
Even the Beatles and the Stones...
...changed their members
right before their debut.
-Chiba cares about this band
more than anyone...
-This isn't a social club!
We can't make it big like that!
Do you really mean that?
If Chiba quits BECK...
I'm quitting too!
Maria seems like a
really aggressive girl.
Oh, her...You better tell
Koyuki to be careful.
Huh?
Maria's a nymphomaniac!
What! Chiba-kun left?!
His whereabouts unknown?
He's turned off his cell phone,
I can't contact him at all.
What about our performance?
Anyway, let's split up
and search for him.
It's 3:00 now,
so we still have 3 hours.
I'll go take a look
at the campsite.
Then, I'll search the stages.
I'll check out the gates.
What a bubbly stage...
My sister's vision of the
Grateful Sound is barely alive.
Seems like there's more
posers than before.
Yeah, but you get to see bands
you wouldn't ordinarily see...
I think it's okay.
Hey, I just saw her panties!
Really?!
I swear!
"Please recycle even if
this station is unmanned."
I swear!
Chiba-kun!
Chiba-kun's things...
Thank goodness.
-Hi, Koyuki.
-Hmm? Maria?
Hey, is it true that guys get high...
...and wanna make love
before the live show starts?
Uh? I don't have time to talk now...
I've got to find...
Hey, Koyuki? What are you doing?
N-no...It's not...Maho!
Chiba-kun...
Where are you, Chiba-kun!?
Mr. Chiba of the Mongolian Chop Squad,
your friends are waiting
for you at the 3rd stage.
I repeat, Mr. Chiba of
the Mongolian Chop Squad...
...your friends are waiting
for you at the 3rd stage.
Maybe...you weren't meant
to be a part of this band.
I'm sorry Taira-kun.
Take care, Koyuki, Saku...
Chiba-kun! I'm sorry,
I made a mistake.
I was planning to go straight home,
but since these guys are here...
Generation 69. If I hadn't met
this band, where would I be now?
Didn't it get a bit chilly?
You think? Wanna eat the pork?
I wonder if BECK's performance
is going to be alright...
She's amazing.
I'm completely her fan now.
Yes, she's the real deal.
But most of the troops are still at the
main stage, or if not, at the second stage...
Can't beat those numbers.
That's absolutely impossible.
To garner more people
than the main stage,
or even the second stage
for that matter.
It would take a miracle.
What's up?
Let's give up.
What?
Eiji's band on the main stage
is booked solid.
Even Malcolm on the second stage,
who's sold over
20 million CDs in the US...
There's no way a band like us on
the third stage can beat those numbers.
And besides, without Chiba,
we can't perform live.
We still have one more hour.
We're searching for Chiba now.
I saw you from the hotel.
What are you doing here
before the stage?
Hey Ryusuke, are you listening? Hey!
You remember what happens
to the loser now, huh?
Yeah, we're having problems
because of that.
Hmph.
You running away?
Yup, I'm more of a pest than I look.
Watch your back, kid.
He really hates you.
Come with me.
I have something for you.
Alright, let's go!
-Let me go! Let me go!
-Hold him down!
Hey, it's cold!
There's no more time left.
Chiba-kun!?
This guy has calmed down
all of a sudden.
Yeah. Malcolm and Belle Ame
are about to start.
Today's main events, huh?
Untie me! I'm going home.
Huh?
If I can't sing from the heart,
then what is this song for...
You're still here, haven't disappeared,
Still going on strong...
Everybody! The ground's
wet and slippery,
so don't push the folks
in front of you!
Then, let me introduce him to you...
Let's call him out here...
All right, here we go...
Yoshito Morozumi!
Hi girls! Are you ready? Okay?!
Morozumi!!
Lying in the bed,
you said, "It's not happen..."
Hey, what's security doing?
We've had injuries
in past performances!
17,000 at the main,
10,200 at the second,
500 at the third stage.
Thanks, man. Keep me posted.
That can't be a good match.
Well, the rain surely fucked up
the equipment on the third stage...
The show hasn't even started.
You may be right.
Hah, these fools are unlucky!
What did you say?!
You're going to withdraw?
It can't be helped.
It won't be a performance
without Chiba and Ryusuke.
Even if we did an
impromptu performance,
it won't be worth a tenth
of our usual show.
That may be true, but what about the 500
people waiting for you out in the rain?
Huh? 500 people? That's amazing!
It's not amazing, compared to
the main and second stages.
They're them, we're us.
That's right!
It doesn't matter how many
Ran and Leon gather together!
You guys replaced the disbanded
band Loud [Crime City].
I can feel you guys are special.
I've been through
3 different bands so far...
2 of which are no longer together.
I don't think BECK has the kind
of chemistry that we used to have.
Taira-kun.
Sato-san, the equipment is almost ready!
500 people...waiting to see us.
Yeah, they're people who've heard
of us through word of mouth.
Honestly, the way things look now,
it might be too hard to meet these
people's expectation of BECK.
Saku, haven't you noticed?
There're several people out there
who always come to our shows.
All the way out here in the mountains,
out in the rain...
Koyuki-kun! Saku-chan!
Wow, Hiromi-chan!
Did you come here by yourself?
You should take a deep breath.
Huh?
That's what I always do
before a tournament.
Oh?
I've never seen both of you
look so uneasy...
Can I...borrow this?
This guitar sounds really great.
Isn't that Jewel's acoustic guitar?
Can I borrow this?
I want to go all out
using this guitar.
Koyuki...
Fine. I'll settle things for you.
Thanks.
The equipment's okay now!
You can start anytime.
Go ahead.
Yeah...
Hey, Koyuki!
I'm going.
Koyuki...
Hey, why's Koyuki by himself?
Hey, that's the kid in
the Dying Breed movie, right?
Was BECK a single artist?
-Koyuki! Hang in there!
-Huh?!
Thank you...everyone.
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion around me
this emotion makes wonder
I will remember when I get it,
it's resting on me
-"I've Got a Feeling",
that's the Beatles, right?
-Yeah.
One morning, I will handle this emotion
-"I've Got a Feeling",
that's the Beatles, right?
-Yeah.
One morning, I will handle this emotion
I want to express this emotion,
this emotion around me
that makes my mind free
Oh yeah...
Hey, is this what
"I've Got a Feeling" sounded like?
That can make this, this emotion
It seems completely different!
Oh...yeah...
Koyuki-kun...This is definitely
your rendition of "I've Got a Feeling."
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion around me
Koyuki-kun...This is definitely
your rendition of "I've Got a Feeling."
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion around me
This song is good!
-Koyuki-kun...
-Koyuki!
That's my buddy up there! Tanaka!
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion makes me wonder
That's my buddy up there! Tanaka!
I can't express this emotion,
this emotion makes me wonder
Hey, you! Can you hear this?!
If you plan on performing,
you'd better do it now!
Oh yeah...
You don't get it, do you?
That can make this, this emotion
There's no way I could just barge in and
keep up with Koyuki's tension out there.
That can make this, this emotion
Just you wait, Koyuki!
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day
What a fool
I don't know 'bout tomorrow
What it's like to be
Ah...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Full moon sways
Smiling in my arms for all those years
Next episode, "Third Stage."
Will I finally be able to
perform at the Grateful Sound?
"Live 24 'Third Stage'"
Will I finally be able to
perform at the Grateful Sound?
"Live 24 'Third Stage'"
I will-!